`  1  2  3  4  5  6  7  8  9  0  ⫶  =
    q  w  e  r  t  y  u  i  o  p  [  ]  \
     a  s  d  f  g  ḫ  j  k  l  :  ʾ
      z  x  š  v  b  n  m  ṣ  ṭ  /

The first 47 characters of this file, ignoring spaces, carriage returns, and
line feeds, define the layout, based on an ANSI physical layout read by rows.
Any further characters are ignored.

I tried coming up with something sensible for QWERTY.

This ended up differing a bit in terms of the US-to-Akkadian mapping from what
I had done for myself with Dvorak, which is:

`  1  2  3  4  5  6  7  8  9  0  [  ]
    ʾ  ⫶  ṭ  p  y  f  g  š  r  l  /  =  \
     a  o  e  u  i  d  ḫ  t  n  s  ṣ
      :  q  j  k  x  b  m  w  v  z

I put ⫶ (which transcribes 𒑳) on [,] and ṣ on [-] for Dvorak, but on QWERTY
that would result in an awkward letter on the number row and a punctuation sign
in between letters.  Swapping those led to ṣ and ṭ being next to each other,
amusingly.

For keyboard shortcuts to work, it matters that ḫ be where you want [H] and š
where you want [C]: I wrote things so Ctrl+š will be sent as Ctrl+C and Ctrl+ḫ
as Ctrl+H.  The placement of the other characters is irrelevant.

Some characters are unused in the sign list (o, y, x, [, ], \, =, `), you can
replace them by whatever you want (as long as it is in the BMP, so not cuneiform
amusingly).
